JACK WITBROCK FINLAY

ADDRESS: 3/12 Clare Place, Mt Wellington, Auckland, New Zealand

EMAIL: jack@jackfinlay.com PHONE: +64 22 603 5912

WEB: jackfinlay.com

GITHUB: github.com/JackWFinlay

Summary

Aspiring to build a successful career in Software Engineering. Constantly seeking to further skills and education through independent study.

Technical Skills

Skill	Experience
C#	3 years
JavaScript	3 years
SQL	4 years
Version Control (Git, GitHub, Bitbucket)	4 years
Databases (SQL Server, Oracle)	3 Years
Agile Methodologies	4 Years
Agile Tools (Jira, TFS, VSTS)	3 Years

Education

Auckland University of Technology, Auckland, New Zealand 2013 - 2016

■ Bachelor of Computer and Information Science - Software Development Major.

Topics covered included: Software Development in C# and Java, Object-Oriented Design and Development, Databases, Agile Methodologies, Information security, Data process Modelling, Project Management, Discrete Mathematics and Linear Algebra, Data Structures, and Algorithms.

Experience

Software Developer March 2018 - Present AlphaCert Labs Itd, Auckland □ C# □ HTML/CSS/Javascript □ ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework □ Microsoft SQL Server ■ SSRS Reporting Full-stack ASP.Net MVC developer role. Primarily developing in C#, HTML/CSS, and JavaScript. ETL and data transformation in C#. SSRS report development. Collaboration with internal and external clients to produce bespoke platform functionality. **Analyst Programmer** August 2016 - March 2018 Gentrack Itd, Auckland ■ BASIC Variant Analysis Debugging ■ Microsoft SQL Server Oracle Database Defect fixes and extension of functionality of utilities billing software. Data analysis and database development using SQL. Collaboration with internal and external clients to achieve consistent results. **Technical Consultant April 2015 - August 2016 Business Mechanix Itd, Auckland** □ C#

Developed a website for international students to find study options in New Zealand. This role also involved managing and mentoring a team of three interns working over the 2015/16 summer. Secondary roles involved setup and management of Azure virtual machines, maintenance of C# applications, and ad-hoc customer support.

□ HTML/CSS/Javascript

□ SPARQL RDF API□ Microsoft SQL Server

☐ ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework

Intern Developer December 2014 - February 2015 University of Auckland IT Services, Auckland

☐ Scriptella☐ Bash

Intern developer role at IT Services. Current and new projects. Reverse engineered an HTTP driver for Scriptella from the source code. Wrote various ad-hoc Scriptella, Groovy and Bash scripts.

References

References available on request